[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
I still don't even know what
this chamber is for.
I don't think I can climb those
beams; there's no grip.
Oh, I know what this is like.
It's like a giant esophagus.
So, I guess this would be the stomach.
Because this could be acid.
I don't know what it is.
So, if that's the stomach,
then where's the...
Hey, what's this?  A ladder!
While, I'm 100% in favor of having
a tomb this size devoted to me,
I shouldn't be put in it
until after I'm dead.
You don't bury the pharaoh alive.
That's what the help is for.
So, if those other guys want to
stay down there and die
to honor my future burial site,
I guess that's okay, but it's
still a little premature.
It would be better if they were
locked in and died as I was being buried.
Man, this is a long climb.
How much farther is it?
Man, y'know, on second thought,
I'm not sure I want to be buried here.
I mean, yeah, the chamber's
big, which is good,
but it's all underground;
nobody's going to see this.
And there needs to be
statues carved of me.
And murals.
They have the right idea with
the Lincoln Memorial.
None of this abstract crap like
the Washington Monument.
I want everybody to know it's me!
Dammit!  How am I going
to get over there?
Oh, is this a ledge?
No, not really, but
it'll have to do.
Jesus Christ, this is not a lot of room.
Why is there a ladder here if
this is the only way to access it?
[exhales]
God, that was almost as bad as
the other elevator shaft.
The one before this one, I think.
The one where the guy died.
I mean, the one where the guy died
that wasn't the first one where
the other guy died.
I-I mean, the one where the
other GUYS died.
I think that's the one.
That one sucked.
Aaaaa!  Yow!
YiyiyiyiyiYIYIYIYIYI!
[gasping]
Yeah, I don't know.
I've been up and down so many
elevators, I'm kind of losing track.
Something is happening.
Y'know, I don't
remember having horrible
electrical shocks going through
here the first time.
I do remember being in pain, though.
I mean, I'm not sure it was this
exact same location,
but that's been pretty consistent.
In fact, if you were to sum up this whole
day in just one word, it would be "pain".
Or maybe "doom".
Or maybe just "bang".
I guess that your vote.
I guess your votes are for "dead".
Though, I don't like "dead".
I think it sends the wrong message.
Oh, God!  Not this again!
Okay, I'll just go slow and face the wall
so if I slip, I'll have
another chance to...
No...
No, no, no...
Okay, that's enough of that.
I never need to do that again.
Oh, jeez.  This is the one
that's really bad.
You know, I don't think of myself
as being afraid of heights,
but look at this!
It's DEEP!
All right,
all right,
all right...
all right....
all right.....
all right......
Raaneeh!
OKAY!  I ROCK!
NOW STOP MAKING ME PROVE IT!
THAT WAS NOT COOL!
God dammit, this thing's
blocking me again!
What's your problem?!
Did you see that jump I made?!
Here, just move!
No....
Okay, I can see there's no
reasoning with you.
You're going to throw a fit, fine!
You know, this is what counseling is for,
but I just don't have time for this.
Here!
This is ridiculous.
You know, that was my last grenade.
Not that I expect you to care
about my feelings.
God, shut up!
Just shut up!
I don't-- I'm not talking to you.
Hey, it just occurred to me.
What if that's only part of--WHOA!
Yeah, that's close enough.
What if this is the monster's
hair strands or something?
And the rest of it teleported
inside the Earth?
It's wearing me and this entire
facility as a hat.
I'm not sure how I feel about that.
I wouldn't go so far and say I
feel dirty, but it's strange.
[tentacles moan]
Yeah.
Yeah, see that moaning doesn't
help anything either.
I mean, what's your motive here?
That's the real question, isn't it?
All you're giving me is this
banging and moaning.
I'm just not ready for this.
I never should've got involved.
I just want to get out of here.
Whoa, whoa, what's this?
Are you kidding me?
Are we using tape reel
computers?
No....
Wait, are those slots for punch cards?
[tentacles moan]
Shut up!
No!
I'm not listening to any more of this.
Hey, the lights are on.
Hey, it's doing something.
Did somebody fix this?
Wait, what did I just do?
Oh!
YEAH!
THAT'S RIGHT!
IF YOU CAN'T TAKE THE HEAT, GET OUT
OF THE ROCKET PROPULSION TEST CHAMBER!
AH HAH HAH HAH!
BURN!
Burn!
Physics rules!